Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Writings and Speeches, 1912-2000 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Open Files, 1912-1993 and undated
  - Reed, Vergil D., (1-7 of 11 folders)
    - 1947. Speech. Look Behind the World Trade Mirror (Box 40)
    - 1947. Speech. Speech at Weco Forum (Box 40)
    - 1948. Other writing. Getting the Most Out of Marketing Research (speech and article, 3 versions) (Box 40)
    - 1948. Article. Good News-and Bad-About Sales (Box 40)
    - 1948. Article. Jackpot for (2 versions) (Box 40)
    - 1948. Article. Jute Industry Faces Real Task in Combating Steady Inroads by Paper (Box 40)
    - 1948. Other writing. Selection, Training, and Supervision of Field Interviewers in Marketing Research (committee report) (Box 40)
    - 1949. Speech. Business Climate and Outlook (Box 40)
    - 1949. Speech. Economic Climate and Outlook (speech and article) (Box 40)
    - 1949. Speech. International Marketing Research (Box 40)
    - 1949. Speech. Modern Marketing Methods for Hosiery Wholesalers (Box 40)
    - 1949. Article. No Cause for Jitters in Business Outlook (Box 40)
    - 1949. Article. Population Trends and Changes in the Next Decade (Box 40)
    - 1949. Article. Recent Developments in Distribution (Box 40)
    - 1949. Speech. West Coast... Basic Trends and Opportunities (Box 40)
    - 1950. Speech. Challenges Facing Food Distributors in the '50s (speech and article) (Box 40)
    - 1950. Other writing. Det Amerikanske Marked for Europaeiske Varer (Danish booklet) (Box 40)
    - 1950. Article. How and Where to Get the Facts for 'Operation Marketing (2 versions) (Box 40)
    - 1950. Speech. New Things in the Census (Box 40)
    - 1950. Speech. Values of Marketing Research (speech and article, 3 versions) (Box 40)
    - 1951. Other writing. How to Use the Census (pamphlet) (Box 40)
    - 1951. Speech. Cupid, the Stork, the Grim Reaper and Your Market (Box 40)
    - 1951. Article. Expanding Commerce Must Be Based on Healthy Balanced Trade (Box 40)
    - 1951. Article. Fastest-Growing Markets in the U.S. (Box 40)
    - 1951. Article. Import Blindness (Box 40)
    - 1951. Article. New Aid to Marketing Men: State Economic Areas (Box 40)
    - 1951. Article. New Look (Box 40)
    - 1951. Speech. Other Side of the World Trade Mirror (Box 40)
    - 1952. Article. American is Growing--Are You? (Box 40)
    - 1952. Speech. Future of Canadian-United States Trade (Box 40)
    - 1952. Article. Look or Two at '52 (Box 40)
    - 1952. Article. Marketing in the Colleges (Box 40)
    - 1952. Speech. New Horizons in International Trade (Box 40)
    - 1952. Article. Outlook for the Home Laundry Industry (Box 40)
    - 1952. Article. What Our Aging Population Means to Marketing (3 versions) (Box 40)
    - 1952. Article. What Our Record Birthrate (Box 40)
    - 1952. Other writing. What's the Potential Sardine Market in Bolivia? (pamphlet) (Box 40)
    - 1953. Article. Are You Talking to Your Prospects as if They Lived in 1900 (by Ruth Reed) (Box 40)
    - 1953. Article. City is Business Capital and World Supermarket (Box 40)
    - 1953. Article. Don't Miss This Gold Mine of Market Data (2 versions) (Box 40)
    - 1953. Article. Russia Calls It Dumpling (Box 40)
    - 1953. Speech. Us Uncultured Americans (2 versions) (Box 40)
    - 1953. Speech. What's Happening to the American Market? (Box 40)
    - 1953. Article. You Don't Have to Die to Win (Box 40)
    - 1954. Article. Changes in Your Market and How You Get There (Box 40)
    - 1954. Speech. Cupid, the Stork, the Grim Reaper, Change, and Your Market (Box 40)
    - 1954. Speech. Is Canada Prepared for Her Economic Future? (Box 40)
    - 1954. Speech. Outlook for 1955 (Box 40)
    - 1954. Speech. What Can or Should a Trade Association Do to Aid its Members With Their Marketing Problems (Box 40)
    - 1955. Article. Ballooning Government Outgrows Business (Box 40)
    - 1955. Speech. Changing in Your Market in the American Economy (speech and pamphlet, 3 versions) (Box 40)
    - 1955. Speech. Economic Look Ahead (Box 40)
    - 1955. Speech. How Can Wholesalers Attune Themselves to Expanding Markets? (Box 40)
    - 1955. Article. How to Get the Most Out of Marketing Research (Box 40)
    - 1956. Speech. Basic Trends in Population (2 versions) (Box 40)
    - 1956. Article. Big Market Growth in Latin America (Box 40)
    - 1956. Speech. Building a Dynamic Appliance Market (Box 40)
    - 1956. Article. Changing Profile of the United States Market (Box 40)
    - 1956. Speech. Consumer Market in Our Economy (Box 40)
    - 1956. Speech. Consumer You'll Meet (Box 40)
    - 1956. Article. Elusive Consumer (Box 40)
    - 1956. Article. General Economic and Farm Market Outlook (Box 40)
    - 1956. Speech. How Many One-Mores Can Your Market Take? (Box 40)
    - 1956. Speech. Latin American Markets (Box 40)
    - 1956. Speech. Speech delivered by Mr. Takeo Komuro (Box 40)
  - Reed, Vergil D. (continued), (8-11 of 11 folders) (Box 41)
    - 1957. Speech. Dynamic American Market (Box 41)
    - 1957. Speech. Our Economy and Your Farm Market (Box 41)
    - 1957. Speech. Our Fruit Basket Market (Box 41)
    - 1958. Article. American Market Today and Tomorrow (Box 41)
    - 1958. Article. Better Marketing: The Key to World Markets and a Higher Standard of Living (also an Italian version) (Box 41)
    - 1958. Article. Changing Farm Market (Box 41)
    - 1958. Speech. Changing Role of the Advertising Agency (Box 41)
    - 1958. Article. Miglior Distributions (Box 41)
    - 1958. Article. Tourism--The Partner of World Trade (Box 41)
    - 1960. Article. EAESP and You (talk on the Escola de Administração de Empresas de São Paolo, the first business college in Latin America) (Box 41)
    - 1960. Article. Motivation Research in Marketing (Box 41)
    - 1960. Article. Sao Paulo School to Become Latin America's First Business College (Box 41)
    - 1960. Speech. Us Uncultured Americans (Box 41)
    - 1961. Speech. Impediments to Foreign Trade (Box 41)
    - 1961. Article. Marketing Research from the Executive Standpoint (Box 41)
    - 1962. Speech. Changing Face of the American market (Box 41)
    - 1963. Speech. Future of Marketing in Argentina (Box 41)
    - 1964. Article. Investigacion de comercializaction desde el punto de vista ejecutivo (Box 41)
    - 1964. Speech. LAFTA--Its Problems and Prospects (Box 41)
    - 1965. Speech. Five Year Extension on the Trade Agreement Acts (Box 41)
    - 1966. Speech. Marketing Research from the Executive Standpoint (Box 41)
    - 1966. Speech. What is Marketing and its Place in the Economy? (Box 41)
    - 1967. Speech. Theory and Analysis of Demand (Box 41)
    - 1969. Speech. Advertising Strategy in Global Marketing (speech and article) (Box 41)
    - 1969. Speech. Around the World in an Hour and a Quarter (Box 41)
    - Undated. Other writing. Broadening Horizons of Business (pamphlet) (Box 41)
  - Reeves, George C.
    - 1950. Article. Badvertising Creates Negative Comments (Box 41)
    - 1951. Speech. New Developments and Progress in Our Interchange on Objectionable Advertising (Box 41)
  - Reichel, Walter
    - 1994. Speech. Beyond Effective Frequency (Box 41)
  - Remiongton, Mahlon G.
    - 1960. Speech. What is Marketing? (2 versions) (Box 41)
  - Resor, Stanley B., (1-3 of 7 folders)
    [Some of Resor's speeches and writings were located in three scrapbooks dating from Resor's purchase of the company in 1916 until 1957, two years prior to his retirement as Chief Executive Officer. A fourth scrapbook, covering the period from 1925 through 1939, has been lost. The scrapbooks also contained clippings, correspondence, pamphlets and other printed materials which accompanied the speeches and writings.]
    - 1916. Speech. Address at Yale (Box 41)
    - 1916. Speech. In class (Box 41)
    - 1916. Speech. To Silk Association (Box 41)
    - 1916. Speech. To Yale Seniors (Box 41)
    - 1917. Speech. Sphinx Club (Box 41)
    - 1917. Speech. What Magazine Advertising is Accomplishing (Box 41)
    - 1918. Other writing. Report of National Committee on Agency Service (AAAA pamphlet) (Box 41)
    - 1918. Speech. Two Means of Saving Labor and Reducing Cost (Box 41)
    - 1919. Speech. Agency and the Representative (Box 41)
    - 1919. Other writing. How Advertising Helps Salesmen (pamphlet) (Box 41)
    - 1919. Article. How One Big Advertising Agency Trains Its Staff to High Efficiency. Associated Advertising, Aug. (Box 41)
    - 1919. Speech. Remarks made at U.S. Rubber Co. salesmen's convention (Box 41)
    - 1920. Speech. For United States Rubber Company convention (Box 41)
    - 1920. Speech. Large Versus Small Agency (Box 41)
    - 1920. Other writing. Letter to a client (Box 41)
    - 1920. Other writing. Letter to the editor, Printer's Ink (Box 41)
    - 1920. Speech. O'Sullivan's salesmen's convention (Box 41)
    - 1920. Speech. Talk to class (Box 41)
    - 1921. Speech. Address at Stanley Insulating Company sales convention (Box 41)
    - 1921. Speech. Do Laws Really Govern Human Action? (Box 41)
    - 1921. Other writing. Individual Effort Has Had Its Day (pamphlet) (Box 41)
    - 1921. Article. Methods of the Big Agency of To-Day. Fourth Estate, Nov. 5 (Box 41)
    - 1923. Other writing. What Do These Changes Mean? (pamphlet) (Box 41)
    - 1924. Speech. Audit Bureau of Circulations from the Point of View of the Agency (Box 41)
    - 1924. Speech. Major Developments I American Advertising During the Past Decade (Box 41)
    - 1924. Speech. New Information (Box 41)
    - 1924. Article. What the American Association of Advertising Agencies Does to Make Advertising Scientifically More Effective. Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science, Sept. (Box 41)
  - Resor, Stanley B. (continued), (4-7 of 7 folders) (Box 42)
    - 1927. Other writing. Advertising as a Career (pamphlet) (Box 42)
    - 1929. Article. Dollar-a-Year Graduate School. Pictorial Review, June (Box 42)
    - 1929. Article. Personalities and the Public (Box 42)
    - 1930. Speech. Press and Its Relation to Public Opinion and Government (Box 42)
    - 1930. Speech. Talk on Cutex and Odorono advertising (Box 42)
    - 1931. Other writing. Publicity Program for the Boys' Club (pamphlet) (Box 42)
    - 1931. Speech. Remarks at new members group meeting (Box 42)
    - 1938. Speech. Growth and Function of the Advertising Agency (Box 42)
    - 1940. Other writing. More Jobs Than Men (pamphlet) (Box 42)
    - 1949. Speech. Acceptance speech, Annual Advertising Awards (Box 42)
    - 1949. Article. Advertising--Some Paradoxes and Parallels. Advertising and Selling, Apr. (Box 42)
    - 1949. Other writing. Facts and the Gaining of Acceptance for Them (pamphlet) (Box 42)
    - 1952. Speech. Fellow Participants in a Great Adventure (Box 42)
    - 1955. Speech. Increasing the Knowledge Available to Management for Advertising Policy Decisions (authorship attributed to James Webb Young) (Box 42)
    - 1956. Article. Selling Ideas. Harvard Crimson Guide to Career Opportunities, Jan. (Box 42)
  - Restall, Robin, (2 folders)
    - 1978. Speech. International Advertising Coordination (Box 42)
    - 1980. Speech. How to Get the Best Out of Your Advertising Agency (Box 42)
    - 1984. Speech. Coordination, a Managers' View (Box 42)
    - Undated. Speech. How to Improve Your International Advertising Through Cross-Breeding (Box 42)
  - Rex, Harriet
    - 1970. Speech. Future Communication to Consumers (Box 42)
  - Reynolds, Donald B.
    - 1965. Article. Merchandiser Tells Why the Drug Store Should Be Where the Action Is. NARD Journal, July 5 (Box 42)
  - Richey, Nunter S.
    - Circa 1920s. Article. Hundred Rules for Being a Business Man (Box 42)
  - Robertson, Donald C., (5 folders)
    - 1973. Speech. What Really Happened as I Cried to My Basic MPP for Mercy (Box 42)
    - 1974. Speech. Advertiser/Agency Relationship--A Positive Force in an Unpredictable Economy (Box 42)
    - 1974. Speech. Challenges for Life Insurance Marketing Posed by Market and Consumer Forces over the Next Decade (Box 42)
    - 1974. Speech. Nationalism--A Reality (Box 42)
    - 1975. Speech. Advertising Agency (Box 42)
    - 1975. Speech. Changing Anatomy of an Advertising Agency (Box 42)
    - 1976. Speech. One International Service Company's Perspective Within a Nationalistic Environment (Box 42)
    - 1976. Speech. People Management at JWT Canada (Box 42)
    - 1977. Speech. Advertiser--Friend or Foe? (Box 42)
    - 1977. Speech. International Marketing Sensitivity (Box 42)
    - 1978. Speech. Agency Management Perspective on the Creative Department (Box 42)
    - 1978. Speech. Observations on Australian Advertising (Box 42)
    - 1979. Speech. North American Perspective on Australian Marketing (Box 42)
    - 1979. Speech. Role of Advertising (Box 42)
    - 1979. Speech. Should Advertising Agencies be Involved Below-the-Line? (Box 42)
    - 1981. Speech. Through the Looking Glass (Box 42)
    - 1982. Speech. Reflections of a Senile Ex-Manager (Box 42)
    - 1983. Speech. J. Walter Thompson: The Evolution of an Owl to a Hawk (Box 42)
    - Undated. Other writing. Troutbeck--Year One Revisited (humor) (Box 42)
  - Robins, Vic
    - 1978. Speech. Generic Labels (Box 42)
  - Rock, Bob
    - 1965. Other writing. South Africa trip report (Box 42)
  - Romano, Andy
    - 1980. Article. They Even Gave It a Woman's Name So They Wouldn't Have to Pay Her as Much. Art Direction, Oct. (Box 42)
  - Rosberg, J. Wesley
    - 1970. Speech. Advertising in Recession Periods (Box 42)
  - Rosenkranc, George
    - 1978-1979. Other writing. Miscellaneous small articles and clippings (Box 42)
  - Ross, William E. (Box 43)
    - 1966. Article. 7-Up is Wet & Wild (Box 43)
    - 1976. Other writing. Agency Leaders Speak Out on Advertising (Ross interview) (Box 43)
    - 1976. Article. Creativity Not Defined By a Sign on the Door (Box 43)
    - 1976. Article. From Hard Times/Hard Sell to Creativity/Economic Comfort (2 versions) (Box 43)
    - 1976. Article. Should Agencies Abolish Creative Department? (Box 43)
  - Rotunno, Marie
    - 1985. Article. Color Me Pink--How 'Bout You? Once Over Lightly, Sept. (Box 43)
  - Rudolph, Peter
    - 1985. Article. Cannes--Return on Investment. J. Walter Thompson News, Dec. (Box 43)
  - Rushmore, Elsie M.
    - 1924. Other writing. Service of Research in the World of Affairs (draft) (Box 43)
    - Undated. Article. Fact Finding in the Advertising Field (Box 43)
  - Rust, John H.
    - 1982. Article. Looking at Magazine Repro. Graphic Arts Buyer, Jan.-Feb. (Box 43)
  - Salorio, Steve
    - 1987. Other writing. Statement on unsolicited ideas (Box 43)
  - Samuels, Gabriel (Gabe)
    - 1982. Speech. Why This Approach Will Produce Better Planning Inputs Than Awareness to GRP Models (Box 43)
  - Saunders, Douglas
    - 1958. Article. Case for Advertising (Box 43)
  - Scaros, Constantine
    - 1977. Speech. Language and Symbols in Advertising (Box 43)
  - Schachte, Henry M., (2 folders)
    - 1963. Speech. Is There a Provable Relationship between Advertising and Sales? (Box 43)
    - 1963. Speech. It's Amateur Night in the ___ Game (speech and article) (Box 43)
    - 1964. Speech. Who Put the Glue in the Marketing Mix? (Box 43)
    - 1965. Speech. General Advertising Speech to Bartlesville (Box 43)
    - 1966. Speech. Advertising Regulation (Box 43)
    - 1966. Speech. Budget, Budget, Who's Got the Budget? (Box 43)
    - 1967. Speech. Advertising Awards Day Speech (Box 43)
    - 1967. Speech. Background of the M.P.A. Free Choice Campaign (Box 43)
    - 1967. Speech. Client Service (see also Peter Gilow Papers) (Box 43)
    - 1967. Speech. Industry and the Future of Our Society (Box 43)
    - 1967. Speech. Marketing--The Path to Increased Profitability (Box 43)
    - 1967. Other writing. Newsstand Scene (recording script), 3 versions (Box 43)
    - 1967. Speech. Simple Complexities of Marketing in America (Box 43)
    - 1968. Speech. Changing World of Thompson (Box 43)
    - 1968. Speech. Closing Speech to Magazine Publishers Association (Box 43)
    - 1968. Speech. Consumerism (Box 43)
    - 1969. Other writing. Advertising Council Annual Dinner (script) (Box 43)
    - 1969. Other writing. Management Control at JWT (draft) (Box 43)
    - 1969. Speech. Morality in the Media (on pornography) (Box 43)
    - 1969. Speech. Speech to ANA Management Seminar (Box 43)
    - 1969. Speech. Speech to Public Relations Managers Mtg. (Box 43)
    - 1969. Speech. Three Marketing Thoughts for the '70s (Box 43)
    - 1970. Speech. Magazine Day--History of Media (Box 43)
    - 1970. Other writing. Minutes of the Advertising Council (script) (Box 43)
    - 1970. Speech. Speech to Religion in American Life (Box 43)
    - 1970. Speech. Speech to Traffic Audit Bureau (Box 43)
    - 1971. Article. Advertising Function (2 versions) (Box 43)
    - 1972. Speech. Communication with the Consumer in Today's Gas Climate (Box 43)
    - 1973. Article. I'm Sure You Remember Snake Oil (Box 43)
    - 1975. Article. Are They (Research Tests) as Good as They Could Be? (Box 43)
    - 1975. Article. Need Ad Research? (Box 43)
    - 1975. Article. Should the Agency Man Jump Ship for the Client in Today's Job Market? (Box 43)
    - 1975. Article. They Did It With Media Magic (Box 43)
    - 1975. Article. Today's Agency Giants are Hiding (Box 43)
    - 1977. Article. Today's (Bad) Corporate Advertising Credo Is: Don't Stick Your Neck Out (Box 43)
  - Schlesinger, Byron
    - 1984. Speech. To AT&T (Box 43)
  - Schwarz, Burkhard, (3 folders)
    - 1979. Speech. JWT Future (Box 43)
  - Schweitzer, Peter, (3 folders)
    - 1985-1992. Other writing. Memoranda and miscellaneous (Box 43)
    - 1989. Other writing. People Buy Brands, Not Products (pamphlet) (Box 43)
    - 1993. Speech. It's a Small World (Box 43)
  - Scollay, John J.
    - 1984. Article. If the U.S. Invented the Supermarket, Who Invented the Hypermarket? JWT News, Dec. (Box 43)
  - Scorse, Gerald
    - 1980. Article. There's Gold in Then Thar' Advertising Books. Magazine Age, Dec. (Box 43)
  - Scott, John
    - 1986. Speech. What Did You Do in the Visual Revolution, Daddy? (Box 43)
  - Scrivener, Robert
    - 1979. Speech. Canada's Incentives for R&D--Are They Competitive? (Box 43)
  - Secunda, Eugene
    - 1979. Speech. Entertainment Advertising (Box 43)
    - 1980. Speech. Movie Advertising on Cable and Satellite (Box 43)
  - Seibert, Wilson
    - 1969. Article. That Boutique Pitch (Box 43)
    - 1978. Speech. Advertising Women of New York (Box 43)
    - 1978. Speech. Not-So-Secret Ingredients of Effective Advertising (Box 43)
    - 1980. Speech. Seminar for JWT Trainees (Box 43)
  - Senior, R. D.
    - 1966. Article. Four Meals a Day: That's Where the Money Goes! (Box 43)
    - 1968. Speech. Challenge of Change in Industrial Marketing (Box 43)
  - Serrille, Lou
    - Circa 1970s. Speech. X Rated Speech (Box 43)
  - Seymour, Dan, (1 of 9 folders)
    - 1962. Speech. Some Things We Have Learned (see also Peter Gilow Papers) (Box 43)
    - 1964. Speech. Communications Unlimited (Box 43)
    - 1965. Speech. Creative Presentation (Box 43)
    - 1965. Speech. Keynote Address (untitled) (Box 43)
    - 1966. Article. How Fast Do You Run to Stand Still? (Box 43)
    - 1966. Speech. Olympic Sports & Mass Media (Box 43)
    - 1966. Speech. Through the Looking Glass (Box 43)
    - 1966. Speech. Untitled (Box 43)
    - 1966. Speech. Untitled (Box 43)
  - Seymour, Dan (continued), (2-6 of 9 folders) (Box 44)
    - 1967. Speech. Chicago Office Meeting Address (Box 44)
    - 1967. Article. Idea Business (Box 44)
    - 1967. Speech. New Reality of Radio (Box 44)
    - 1967. Speech. Remarks (Box 44)
    - 1967. Speech. Where Do We Stand Today? (Box 44)
    - 1967. Speech. Who's Afraid of the Changing World? (Box 44)
    - 1968. Speech. Agency Looks at Direct Mail (Box 44)
    - 1968. Speech. Challenge in International Communications to the Business World (Box 44)
    - 1968. Speech. Comments to JWT Personnel in Canada (Box 44)
    - 1968. Speech. Company Dinner Speech (Box 44)
    - 1968. Speech. Force of Television (Box 44)
    - 1968. Article. New Role of Business in Society (Box 44)
    - 1968. Speech. Toward the Consumer Revolution or Business: The Third Force (Box 44)
    - 1968. Speech. Untitled (Box 44)
    - 1968. Article. View from the Top (Box 44)
    - 1968. Speech. What to Watch in the World Today (Box 44)
    - 1969. Speech. Big Take-Over (Box 44)
    - 1969. Speech. Closed Circuit Talk on JWT Going Public (Box 44)
    - 1969. Speech. How to Go Into the Seventies (Box 44)
    - 1969. Speech. London Special Meeting Talk (Box 44)
    - 1969. Speech. Morgan Stanley Speech (Box 44)
    - 1969. Speech. Remarks (Box 44)
    - 1969. Speech. Will You Find Happiness with the Establishment? (Box 44)
    - 1969. Speech. World of Change--World of Hope (Box 44)
    - 1970. Article. Biggest Boom in History (Box 44)
    - 1970. Speech. Brave New World? (Box 44)
    - 1970. Speech. Chicago International Film Festival (Box 44)
    - 1970. Speech. Comments at Account Representative seminar (Box 44)
    - 1970. Speech. Communications in the Seventies (Box 44)
    - 1970. Article. Great Decisions & the Next Generation (Box 44)
    - 1970. Speech. Management of Change (Box 44)
    - 1970. Speech. New Responsibilities of Business (Box 44)
    - 1970. Speech. Opening Remarks, FDA Chairmen's Meeting (Box 44)
  - Seymour, Dan (continued), (7-9 of 9 folders) (Box 45)
    - 1970. Speech. Presentation to JWT Company Stockholders (Box 45)
    - 1970. Speech. Presentation to Security Analysts (Box 45)
    - 1970. Speech. Shape of the Seventies (Box 45)
    - 1970. Speech. Talk to JWT Chicago (Box 45)
    - 1970. Speech. Untitled (Box 45)
    - 1971. Speech. Design of Change (Box 45)
    - 1971. Speech. International Opportunity (Box 45)
    - 1971. Speech. Real Battle of the Century (Box 45)
    - 1971. Speech. Speech (Box 45)
    - 1971. Speech. Way to Go (Box 45)
    - 1972. Speech. Five New Imperatives for the Seventies (Box 45)
    - 1972. Speech. Gentle Art of Survival (Box 45)
    - 1972. Speech. Opening Remarks (Box 45)
    - 1972. Speech. Speech (Box 45)
    - 1972. Speech. Tarrytown (Box 45)
    - 1972. Speech. Two Cheers for Change (Box 45)
    - 1973. Speech. Advertising Outlook (Box 45)
    - 1973. Speech. Credibility Crisis (Box 45)
    - 1973. Speech. Speech (Box 45)
    - 1973. Speech. Winning the Fight for Consumer Attention (Box 45)
    - 1973. Speech. You Gotta Believe (Box 45)
  - Sharfman, William L.
    - 1982. Speech. National Emergency Executive Briefing on Product Tampering (Box 45)
  - Sherman, Ronald
    - 1967. Article. What's It Like Working for the World's Largest Advertising Agency? (Box 45)
    - 1978. Article. People--A New York Office Perspective (Box 45)
  - Shillinglaw, Selwyn (Sel)
    - Undated. Article. What Price TV Commercials? (Box 45)
  - Simrod, Shelia
    - Undated. Article. Style Opening is Looking Glass (Box 45)
  - Skelly, Florence
    - 1983. Speech. Changes Emerging in the 1980s (Box 45)
  - Smilde, Lubertus
    - 1962. Speech. European Economic Community (Box 45)
    - 1961. Speech. Statement of Lubertus Smilde, Economist (Box 45)
    - 1962. Speech. Major U.S. Population Factors Affecting Media (Box 45)
    - 1962. Article. Marketing, Media and the Big Census (2 versions) (Box 45)
    - Undated. Speech. New Sources for Foreign Market Research (Box 45)
  - Smith, J. Walker
    - 1996. Speech. Cybercitizens (Box 45)
  - Snell, Richard
    - 1989. Speech. Acknowledging Failure (Box 45)
  - Soler, A.R.
    - 1993. Speech. Why Most Advertising Agencies Will Not Survive the '90s (Box 45)
  - Soloman, Debbie
    - 1984. Article. Foreign Circulation. Marketing and Media Decisions, June (Box 45)
    - 1984. Article. How to Use Subscriber Studies. Magazine Age, May (Box 45)